Yo. I'm going to tell you
something that cost me weeks.
Real weeks.
Not "I lost a couple hours" weeks.
I mean full rebuilds.
Started-over-from-scratch weeks.
And nobody warned me
it was coming.
I run five businesses
out of West Palm Beach.
A restaurant.
A courier company.
A trading education brand.
A content funnel engine.
And the legal structure
holding it all together.
All under one roof
called MysterMyself.
Scott-King Coast. One ecosystem.
And I decided to let AI run
the day-to-day operations.
Not just one AI.
A whole team of them.
Claude for strategy.
Kiro for code.
Cowork for desktop automation.
The whole stack working together.
Sounds futuristic right? It is.
Until you hit the wall.
Here's the thing nobody
warns you about.
These AI agents?
They don't remember anything.
Nothing. Zero.
You have a two hour session.
You build something incredible.
You map out your whole system.
You explain your brand.
Your characters. Your colors.
Your rules. You go deep.
You explain that Trading Chef
is the avatar.
You explain the six districts.
You explain the ten characters.
Everything is perfect.
The agent understands.
You're cooking.
Then you close that window.
And it's gone. All of it. Erased.
Next session? That agent has
no idea who you are.
No idea what you built yesterday.
No idea that your brand color
is Gold, not yellow.
No idea that your handle
is @mysterycartel.
No idea that you have ten locked
characters that cannot be changed.
No idea that you already built
half the website.
It just starts fresh.
Every single time.
Like you never met.
I'm not exaggerating.
I lost entire product builds
because an agent invented
new characters that don't exist
in my world.
It changed my color palette
without asking.
Called my brand the wrong name.
Made up features I never approved.
Added a seventh district
when I only have six.
Created an eleventh character
when I only have ten.
And the worst part?
I didn't catch it until
three sessions later.
By then everything
was tangled up.
I had code referencing things
that shouldn't exist.
Pages built for characters
nobody created.
The whole thing was a mess.
That's the problem.
AI has amnesia.
And if you're building anything
serious with it,
anything with a brand,
characters, rules, a world...
that amnesia will destroy
your work quietly.
You won't even notice
until it's too late.
So I fixed it.
I built my own system
from scratch.
Three pieces that work together.
And it changed everything
about how I use AI.
That's what this series is about.
I'm calling it
The Claude Chronicles.
Let's get into it.
First thing I built was what I
call canon anchors.
This is the foundation.
Without this, nothing else works.
Think about it like this.
You're building a world.
Not just a product. A world.
I'm building Scott-King Coast.
It has six districts.
Route Harbor
for courier operations.
Market Marina
for trading education.
Flavor District for food.
Blueprint Bay for legal.
Creator Pier for content.
Legacy Point
for intellectual property.
Six districts. Each one locked.
It has characters. Trading Chef.
That's my avatar.
Black male, chef hat, apron,
gold chain, glasses.
Confident. Urban cartoon style.
Then there's Candle Kid. Wickie.
Louie Liquidity. Chef Goldie.
Grandma Market. Nana Value.
Melissa Mayhem. Melody Mayhem.
Rico Rhythm. Ten characters total.
Each one locked. No agent
can invent an eleventh.
It has colors.
Black. Gold. Red. Green.
Fire Orange. That's the palette.
Locked.
No agent can decide "hey let's
add some blue in there." No.
It has rules.
The handle is always
@mysterycartel.
The avatar always has the chef
hat, the apron, the gold chain.
Always urban cartoon style.
The brand name is always
MysterMyself.
No abbreviations.
No alternate spellings.
No nicknames.
None of that can change without
my explicit approval. Period.
So what did I do?
I wrote it all down in one file.
A canon document.
One source of truth.
And I told every single agent
in my system:
before you do anything,
before you write one line
of code,
before you draft one piece
of content, read this file first.
If what you're about to create
contradicts this file
in any way, stop. Don't do it.
That's a canon anchor.
It's a fixed point in space
that cannot drift.
No matter how creative
the AI wants to get,
it has boundaries. It has laws.
Before I had this? Chaos.
Agents would invent characters
I never created.
They'd add districts
that don't exist.
They'd change my slogan.
They'd use the wrong handle.
They'd describe my avatar
without the gold chain.
Small things. Tiny details.
But they compound into a mess
that takes days to untangle.
Now? The canon is law.
The agents read it at the start
of every session.
They cannot drift because
the anchor holds them in place.
Like a ship tied to a dock.
The water moves. The ship stays.
Simple concept.
Not complicated to implement.
But it changed everything about
the quality of what my agents
produce.
Canon anchors solve
the "what is true" problem.
But there's a second problem
that's just as bad.
The "where were we" problem.
Let me paint the picture.
Monday I'm working with Kiro
on the website.
We fix three bugs
on the homepage.
We update the navigation to
include all six districts.
We start building a new page
for the Trading Chef
tutorial system
but don't finish it.
Good session. Productive.
We made progress.
Tuesday I come back.
Open a new session.
The agent doesn't know
any of that happened.
It doesn't know
what bugs we fixed.
Doesn't know
the navigation changed.
Doesn't know there's a
half-built page sitting
in the codebase.
As far as it knows,
nothing happened yesterday.
So what does it do? It guesses.
It looks at the code and tries
to figure out the current state.
Or worse, it starts suggesting
things we already tried.
It re-introduces bugs
we already fixed.
It suggests building a page
that already half-exists.
It proposes changes to code
that already changed.
You end up going backwards.
Undoing progress.
Fighting your own system.
Session state management
solves this.
And it's simpler than you think.
Here's how I do it.
At the end of every working
session, the agent writes
a memory block. Plain English.
What was built. What was changed.
What files were modified.
What's still pending.
What was approved by me.
What was rejected by me.
What needs to happen next.
It's like shift notes
at a restaurant.
The dinner crew writes down
what happened during their shift
so the morning crew
knows what's up.
No surprises. No repeated work.
Next session starts?
First thing the agent does
is read those memory blocks.
The latest entries.
It knows exactly
where we left off.
What we accomplished.
What's still open.
No guessing. No repeating work.
No re-introducing bugs
we already squashed.
I keep these in a file
called MEMORY-BLOCKS.
It's a running log
in the docs folder.
Every session adds to it.
The agent reads the latest
entries and picks up
like we never stopped talking.
Like a real person
coming back from lunch.
They don't forget the entire
morning just because
they ate a sandwich.
It's not complicated technology.
It's just discipline baked
into the system.
The system writes its own
context at the end.
The system reads its own
context at the start.
The human, that's me,
doesn't have to repeat
themselves every single session.
I don't have to
re-explain my brand.
I don't have to re-explain
what we built yesterday.
The system already knows.
That's session state management.
Your AI picks up where
it left off. Every time.
Automatically.
Here's where it gets
really interesting.
I don't use one agent.
I use four. Working together.
Like a team.
Claude handles strategy.
Big picture thinking. Writing.
Planning.
Architecture decisions.
When I need to think through
a problem or plan a new feature,
that's Claude.
Kiro handles code.
Building features.
Git operations. Pull requests.
Pushing to production.
When something needs to get
built and deployed, that's Kiro.
Cowork handles my desktop.
Moving files between folders.
Opening applications.
Local file management.
Anything that requires touching
my actual computer,
that's Cowork.
GitHub is the source of truth.
The repo.
Everything lives there.
If it's not in the repo,
it doesn't exist.
Four agents. One system.
And they have to talk to each
other without me
playing telephone.
That's relay agent architecture.
It works exactly
like a relay race.
One runner does their leg
of the track.
Then they pass the baton
to the next runner.
Clean handoff. Full speed.
No dropped context.
No fumbled baton.
Here's how a real task flows
through my system.
I tell Claude what I want.
"Build me a thumbnail system
for the YouTube channel."
Claude thinks about it.
Writes the strategy.
Figures out the file structure.
Defines the acceptance criteria.
Then Claude drops a relay task
into an inbox folder
on my desktop.
Kiro picks up that relay task.
Reads it.
Has everything it needs.
The what. The why.
The constraints.
The exact files to create.
Kiro executes. Writes the code.
Pushes it to a branch.
Creates a pull request.
Reports back.
I never touch the terminal.
Never type a git command.
Never open VS Code.
Never install a package.
I just say what I want
in plain English
and the relay handles the rest.
But here's the key
that makes it work.
Each agent knows its role
and only its role.
Claude doesn't try
to write code.
Kiro doesn't try to do strategy.
Cowork doesn't try
to push to GitHub.
They stay in their lane.
No overlap. No confusion.
And the handoff document?
That relay task? That's the baton.
It contains everything the next
agent needs to execute
without asking questions.
The full context.
The instructions.
The constraints. The brand rules.
The acceptance criteria.
Everything pre-loaded.
No ambiguity. No re-explaining.
No "hey can you remind me
what we're doing?"
The baton carries the truth.
That's what makes this
work at scale.
Five businesses. Four agents.
One system. Zero confusion.
I wake up and my agents already
know what to do
because the system tells them.
Look. I'm not a developer.
I don't have a computer
science degree.
I'm a CEO from West Palm Beach
running a restaurant,
a courier company,
a trading brand, a content
engine, and the legal
holding company that ties
it all together.
I'm not sitting here writing
Python or debugging JavaScript.
But I needed a system where
I could say what I want
and it gets built.
Correctly. Every time.
Without me babysitting it.
Without me repeating myself
every session.
Without my brand drifting
off course.
Three pieces.
That's the whole system.
Canon anchors make sure the AI
never forgets what's true.
The characters. The districts.
The colors. The rules. Locked.
Session state makes sure the AI
never forgets what happened.
What we built yesterday.
What's pending.
What's approved. Continuous.
Relay architecture makes sure
multiple agents work together
without stepping on each other.
Clean handoffs. Clear roles.
No confusion.
That's it. That's the system.
And it runs every single day
across all five of my businesses
without me touching a terminal
or writing a single line of code.
If you're building with AI
right now
and you're frustrated because
it keeps forgetting things,
keeps contradicting itself,
keeps making you repeat the same
context over and over...
this is the fix.
It's not a smarter prompt.
It's not a better model.
It's structure.
It's about building a smarter
system around the model.
Give it anchors.
Give it memory. Give it a relay.
Then get out of the way.
This is The Claude Chronicles.
I'm going to show you
everything.
How I built it step by step.
How it breaks when it breaks.
How I fix it.
The real files.
The real workflows.
The real problems
and the real solutions.
No theory. No corporate fluff.
Just a guy from the 561 running
five businesses
with AI agents
that actually deliver.
Follow @mysterycartel on Rumble.
Hit subscribe.
Next episode I'm going deep on
how the canon documents work.
The exact format. The exact
rules.
How to write them so your agents
physically cannot ignore them.
Chef's Golden Rule:
A recipe without measurements
is just a wish.
Your AI needs measurements too.
See you next time.